https://performance-curve.com/privacy-policy

Categories
Alignment / SteeringAcuraAudiBMWBuickCadillacChevrolet / GMCChryslerDodgeEagleFordHondaHyundaiInfinitiIsuzuJeepKiaLexusLincolnMazdaMercuryMiniMitsubishiNissanOldsmobilePlymouthPontiacRAMSaabSaturnScionSubaruSuzukiToyotaVolkswagenVolvoHummerInternationalMercedesCatalytic ConvertersDieselDirect FitAcuraMDXTLAudiA4A4 QuattroBuickEnclaveLeSabrePark AvenueCadillacEscaladeDeVilleChevrolet / GMCAcadiaAvalancheBlazer / JimmyCamaroCaptiva SportCobaltColorado / CanyonEquinoxHHRSilverado / Sierra / TruckSuburbanTahoeTerrainTraverseMalibuChrysler300PacificaTown & CountryDodgeChargerChallengerDakotaGrand CaravanRAMFordContourEdgeEscapeExplorerF-SeriesFusionMustangHondaAccordOdysseyPilotRidgelineCR-VHummerH3IsuzuI-290I-350JeepCherokeeLibertyWranglerGrand CherokeeLexusRX330LincolnMKXMazdaProtegeTributeMercuryCougarMarinerMilanMystiqueMitsubishiEclipseEndeavorGalantMonteroNissanAltimaEquatorFrontierMaximaPathfinderSentraXterraX-TrailPontiacG5G6VibeBonnivilleSaturnAuraIonVueOutlookSubaruForesterImprezaLegacyOutbackSuzukiEquatorToyotaCamryCorollaHighlanderMatrixSiennaSolaraVolkswagenBeetleJettaRoutanUniversal FitMetallic SubstrateCutoutsElectric CutoutKitsManual CutoutDirect Fit CutoutsAccessoriesDiesel Exhaust / ComponentsAccessories / ComponentsClampsRain CapsBendsCatalytic ConvertersDelete, Turbo & Down PipesCumminsDuramaxPowerstrokeECODIESELEGR KitsExhaust SystemsChevy / GMC - DuramaxDodge / RAM - CumminsFord - PowerstrokeNissan - CumminsMufflersPipesStacksTipsEquipmentParts WashersPipe BendersTooling / AccessoriesRod BendersExhaust ComponentsAccessoriesClampsFlangesGasketsHangersO2 Sensor BungsRain CapsBends2"2.25"2.5"3"3.5"4"5"CollectorsFlex PipesDirect Fit FlexUniversal Fit FlexReducers / CouplersTubingTurn Downs"X" and "Y" PipesExhaust SystemsKit ComponentsAcuraIntegraRSXBuickGSSkylarkGran SportCadillacOE Pipes / MufflersChevrolet / GMCAvalancheOE Pipes / MufflersBel AirBiscayneBlazer / JimmyCamaroChevelleColorado / CanyonCorvetteCruzeEl CaminoImpalaMalibuNovaS10 PickupSilverado / Sierra / TruckDuramaxOE Pipes / MufflersSuburbanOE Pipes / MufflersTahoeOE Pipes / MufflersYukon / Yukon XLOE Pipes / MufflersChrysler300AspenDodge / RAMAvengerChallengerChargerCoronetDakotaDartDurangoMagnumRAMCumminsFordBroncoExpeditionExplorerF SeriesPowerstrokeFairlaneFocusMustangRangerHondaOE Pipes / MufflersJeepCherokeeOE Pipes / MufflersGrand CherokeeOE Pipes / MufflersWranglerOE Pipes / MufflersKiaStingerLincolnMark LTNavigatorMazdaMiataNissan370ZFrontierTitanOldsmobileCutlassPlymouthBelvedereDusterGTXRoad RunnerSatelliteValiantPontiacFirebirdGTOLeMansToyotaTacomaOE Pipes / MufflersTundraOE Pipes / MufflersHeadersLightingWork LightsMufflersFlowmasterSuper 1010 Series - Race Muffler30 Seires - Race MufflerOriginal 40Super 40Super 4440 Series - Race MufflerDelta Flow 4050 Big Block50 HD50 Delta FlowSuper 5060 Delta Flow70 Big Block II80 Cross-FlowSuper HP-2Outlaw SeriesDBX SeriesPro SeriesMagnaFlow3.5" x 7" Oval4" x 9" Oval5" x 8" Oval5" x 11" Oval4" Round5" Round6" Round7" Round7" Round - DieselGlasspacksRace MufflersMufflers with TipsXL - 3 ChamberCherry BombExtremeGlasspacksM-80VortexWicked FlowXleratorBudget PerformanceOne ChamberTwo ChamberStraight ThroughOne ChamberTwo ChamberThree ChamberResonators & Glass PacksTruck MufflersOther MufflersRace MufflersTurbo MufflersMuffler & Tips ComboDirect FitOxygen SensorsTipsAngle CutBlack ChromeBlack Powder CoatedCamaro StyleDieselDouble WallDual OutletOvalResonatedSpecialty TipsStraight CutTruckTurn Down
Performance-Curve
My Cart:
0 item(s) - $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
0
Search:
Search
Products
Categories
Alignment / SteeringAcuraAudiBMWBuickCadillacChevrolet / GMCChryslerDodgeEagleFordHondaHyundaiInfinitiIsuzuJeepKiaLexusLincolnMazdaMercuryMiniMitsubishiNissanOldsmobilePlymouthPontiacRAMSaabSaturnScionSubaruSuzukiToyotaVolkswagenVolvoHummerInternationalMercedesCatalytic ConvertersDieselDirect FitAcuraMDXTLAudiA4A4 QuattroBuickEnclaveLeSabrePark AvenueCadillacEscaladeDeVilleChevrolet / GMCAcadiaAvalancheBlazer / JimmyCamaroCaptiva SportCobaltColorado / CanyonEquinoxHHRSilverado / Sierra / TruckSuburbanTahoeTerrainTraverseMalibuChrysler300PacificaTown & CountryDodgeChargerChallengerDakotaGrand CaravanRAMFordContourEdgeEscapeExplorerF-SeriesFusionMustangHondaAccordOdysseyPilotRidgelineCR-VHummerH3IsuzuI-290I-350JeepCherokeeLibertyWranglerGrand CherokeeLexusRX330LincolnMKXMazdaProtegeTributeMercuryCougarMarinerMilanMystiqueMitsubishiEclipseEndeavorGalantMonteroNissanAltimaEquatorFrontierMaximaPathfinderSentraXterraX-TrailPontiacG5G6VibeBonnivilleSaturnAuraIonVueOutlookSubaruForesterImprezaLegacyOutbackSuzukiEquatorToyotaCamryCorollaHighlanderMatrixSiennaSolaraVolkswagenBeetleJettaRoutanUniversal FitMetallic SubstrateCutoutsElectric CutoutKitsManual CutoutDirect Fit CutoutsAccessoriesDiesel Exhaust / ComponentsAccessories / ComponentsClampsRain CapsBendsCatalytic ConvertersDelete, Turbo & Down PipesCumminsDuramaxPowerstrokeECODIESELEGR KitsExhaust SystemsChevy / GMC - DuramaxDodge / RAM - CumminsFord - PowerstrokeNissan - CumminsMufflersPipesStacksTipsEquipmentParts WashersPipe BendersTooling / AccessoriesRod BendersExhaust ComponentsAccessoriesClampsFlangesGasketsHangersO2 Sensor BungsRain CapsBends2"2.25"2.5"3"3.5"4"5"CollectorsFlex PipesDirect Fit FlexUniversal Fit FlexReducers / CouplersTubingTurn Downs"X" and "Y" PipesExhaust SystemsKit ComponentsAcuraIntegraRSXBuickGSSkylarkGran SportCadillacOE Pipes / MufflersChevrolet / GMCAvalancheOE Pipes / MufflersBel AirBiscayneBlazer / JimmyCamaroChevelleColorado / CanyonCorvetteCruzeEl CaminoImpalaMalibuNovaS10 PickupSilverado / Sierra / TruckDuramaxOE Pipes / MufflersSuburbanOE Pipes / MufflersTahoeOE Pipes / MufflersYukon / Yukon XLOE Pipes / MufflersChrysler300AspenDodge / RAMAvengerChallengerChargerCoronetDakotaDartDurangoMagnumRAMCumminsFordBroncoExpeditionExplorerF SeriesPowerstrokeFairlaneFocusMustangRangerHondaOE Pipes / MufflersJeepCherokeeOE Pipes / MufflersGrand CherokeeOE Pipes / MufflersWranglerOE Pipes / MufflersKiaStingerLincolnMark LTNavigatorMazdaMiataNissan370ZFrontierTitanOldsmobileCutlassPlymouthBelvedereDusterGTXRoad RunnerSatelliteValiantPontiacFirebirdGTOLeMansToyotaTacomaOE Pipes / MufflersTundraOE Pipes / MufflersHeadersLightingWork LightsMufflersFlowmasterSuper 1010 Series - Race Muffler30 Seires - Race MufflerOriginal 40Super 40Super 4440 Series - Race MufflerDelta Flow 4050 Big Block50 HD50 Delta FlowSuper 5060 Delta Flow70 Big Block II80 Cross-FlowSuper HP-2Outlaw SeriesDBX SeriesPro SeriesMagnaFlow3.5" x 7" Oval4" x 9" Oval5" x 8" Oval5" x 11" Oval4" Round5" Round6" Round7" Round7" Round - DieselGlasspacksRace MufflersMufflers with TipsXL - 3 ChamberCherry BombExtremeGlasspacksM-80VortexWicked FlowXleratorBudget PerformanceOne ChamberTwo ChamberStraight ThroughOne ChamberTwo ChamberThree ChamberResonators & Glass PacksTruck MufflersOther MufflersRace MufflersTurbo MufflersMuffler & Tips ComboDirect FitOxygen SensorsTipsAngle CutBlack ChromeBlack Powder CoatedCamaro StyleDieselDouble WallDual OutletOvalResonatedSpecialty TipsStraight CutTruckTurn Down
My Account
My Wishlist
My Cart
Checkout
Log In
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Performance Curve - This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data").
This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this …
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that ...
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.
Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of (add date) and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Categories
Alignment / SteeringAcuraAudiBMWBuickCadillacChevrolet / GMCChryslerDodgeEagleFordHondaHyundaiInfinitiIsuzuJeepKiaLexusLincolnMazdaMercuryMiniMitsubishiNissanOldsmobilePlymouthPontiacRAMSaabSaturnScionSubaruSuzukiToyotaVolkswagenVolvoHummerInternationalMercedesCatalytic ConvertersDieselDirect FitAcuraMDXTLAudiA4A4 QuattroBuickEnclaveLeSabrePark AvenueCadillacEscaladeDeVilleChevrolet / GMCAcadiaAvalancheBlazer / JimmyCamaroCaptiva SportCobaltColorado / CanyonEquinoxHHRSilverado / Sierra / TruckSuburbanTahoeTerrainTraverseMalibuChrysler300PacificaTown & CountryDodgeChargerChallengerDakotaGrand CaravanRAMFordContourEdgeEscapeExplorerF-SeriesFusionMustangHondaAccordOdysseyPilotRidgelineCR-VHummerH3IsuzuI-290I-350JeepCherokeeLibertyWranglerGrand CherokeeLexusRX330LincolnMKXMazdaProtegeTributeMercuryCougarMarinerMilanMystiqueMitsubishiEclipseEndeavorGalantMonteroNissanAltimaEquatorFrontierMaximaPathfinderSentraXterraX-TrailPontiacG5G6VibeBonnivilleSaturnAuraIonVueOutlookSubaruForesterImprezaLegacyOutbackSuzukiEquatorToyotaCamryCorollaHighlanderMatrixSiennaSolaraVolkswagenBeetleJettaRoutanUniversal FitMetallic SubstrateCutoutsElectric CutoutKitsManual CutoutDirect Fit CutoutsAccessoriesDiesel Exhaust / ComponentsAccessories / ComponentsClampsRain CapsBendsCatalytic ConvertersDelete, Turbo & Down PipesCumminsDuramaxPowerstrokeECODIESELEGR KitsExhaust SystemsChevy / GMC - DuramaxDodge / RAM - CumminsFord - PowerstrokeNissan - CumminsMufflersPipesStacksTipsEquipmentParts WashersPipe BendersTooling / AccessoriesRod BendersExhaust ComponentsAccessoriesClampsFlangesGasketsHangersO2 Sensor BungsRain CapsBends2"2.25"2.5"3"3.5"4"5"CollectorsFlex PipesDirect Fit FlexUniversal Fit FlexReducers / CouplersTubingTurn Downs"X" and "Y" PipesExhaust SystemsKit ComponentsAcuraIntegraRSXBuickGSSkylarkGran SportCadillacOE Pipes / MufflersChevrolet / GMCAvalancheOE Pipes / MufflersBel AirBiscayneBlazer / JimmyCamaroChevelleColorado / CanyonCorvetteCruzeEl CaminoImpalaMalibuNovaS10 PickupSilverado / Sierra / TruckDuramaxOE Pipes / MufflersSuburbanOE Pipes / MufflersTahoeOE Pipes / MufflersYukon / Yukon XLOE Pipes / MufflersChrysler300AspenDodge / RAMAvengerChallengerChargerCoronetDakotaDartDurangoMagnumRAMCumminsFordBroncoExpeditionExplorerF SeriesPowerstrokeFairlaneFocusMustangRangerHondaOE Pipes / MufflersJeepCherokeeOE Pipes / MufflersGrand CherokeeOE Pipes / MufflersWranglerOE Pipes / MufflersKiaStingerLincolnMark LTNavigatorMazdaMiataNissan370ZFrontierTitanOldsmobileCutlassPlymouthBelvedereDusterGTXRoad RunnerSatelliteValiantPontiacFirebirdGTOLeMansToyotaTacomaOE Pipes / MufflersTundraOE Pipes / MufflersHeadersLightingWork LightsMufflersFlowmasterSuper 1010 Series - Race Muffler30 Seires - Race MufflerOriginal 40Super 40Super 4440 Series - Race MufflerDelta Flow 4050 Big Block50 HD50 Delta FlowSuper 5060 Delta Flow70 Big Block II80 Cross-FlowSuper HP-2Outlaw SeriesDBX SeriesPro SeriesMagnaFlow3.5" x 7" Oval4" x 9" Oval5" x 8" Oval5" x 11" Oval4" Round5" Round6" Round7" Round7" Round - DieselGlasspacksRace MufflersMufflers with TipsXL - 3 ChamberCherry BombExtremeGlasspacksM-80VortexWicked FlowXleratorBudget PerformanceOne ChamberTwo ChamberStraight ThroughOne ChamberTwo ChamberThree ChamberResonators & Glass PacksTruck MufflersOther MufflersRace MufflersTurbo MufflersMuffler & Tips ComboDirect FitOxygen SensorsTipsAngle CutBlack ChromeBlack Powder CoatedCamaro StyleDieselDouble WallDual OutletOvalResonatedSpecialty TipsStraight CutTruckTurn Down
Information
About Us
Privacy Policy
Return & Refund Policy
Shipping Policy
Terms and Conditions
Help Center
Site Map
